	



	Plugin Name: Dr.Modus
	Developer Name: Drummer Modus Team
	Type: VST3 Instrument 
	Description: Drum Module
	Operating System: Windows x64
	Formats: wav, VST3 (VST is a trademark of Steinberg Soft- und Hardware GmbH)	
	System requirements: 
	• Windows 7x64 and higher


	Drummer Modus Team are:
	Additional modules developed by Max Brezhestovski.
	Graphic design and testing by Vera Kinter.
	SynthEdit programming by Max Brezhestovski.
	
	Thanks to Jeff McClintock.
		

	Notes about the C o n t r o l s:

	[Ctrl] key works on:
	• Drum Slot arrows to hear the selected sample;
	• Tune slider (reset);
	• Drum Pad (opens 'set MIDI Note' pop-up);
	• MIDI Note Generator button (opens 'signature' pop-up).

	Holding Tune and Decay arrows simulates repeating clicks.

	PAN knob can be reset by double-clicking.
	
	Clicking on the drum slot's number displays the path of the loaded sample.
	


	M I D I   C o n t r o l l e r   assignments:

Pitch, Decay, Pan, and Volume can be assigned to MIDI controllers by right-clicking on the control and selecting Learn/Unlearn from the pop-up menu that appears.
			


			SynthEdit copyright © 2000-2025 Jeff McClintock.
			https://www.synthedit.com

			Graphics by Vera Kinter. 
			© 2025 Vera Kinter http://www.artvera-music.com
			
			Third party modules by:
			Max Brezhestovski ©2025 https://github.com/maxbreges

			Programming by mbreges © 2025 Max Brezhestovski. 
					Use it at your own risk.
			
			x64 version of the KVR DC 2007 entry.
			
			
			VST is a trademark of Steinberg Soft- und Hardware GmbH
			



